Hey, what's up? I'm Tom.
>> I'm Zendaya.
>> Jon.
>> I'm Sadie.
>> I'm Jacob.
>> And today, with the cast of Spider-Man:
Brand New Day, we are taking GQ's pop
quiz.
Round one, general comic trivia.
>> Oh, no.
>> What iconic line did Uncle Ben say to
Peter Parker?
>> Oh, damn it.
>> With great power comes great
responsibility.
>> Perfect.
Next question. Who created Spider-Man?
>> Oh, yeah.
>> Oh,
>> Stan Lee and Steve Ditko.
>> Wow.
>> What the Tom met.
What supervillain does Ned Leeds become
in the comics?
>> The Hobgoblin.
>> That's correct.
It's going to get harder, guys. What did
Mary Jane say to Peter the first time
>> Face it, tiger. You won. I'm like, you
[clears throat and laughter] Face it,
tiger. Face it, tiger.
>> Just I'm going to I'm going to be I'm
going to hold on. If someone can pull
out the full sentence.
>> the jackpot.
>> Face it, tiger. You hit the jackpot.
>> There you go. That's correct. Points to
Zendaya.
>> I really did.
>> All right.
Which issue of The Amazing Spider-Man
did the Punisher first appear?
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> I actually know this.
>> Which issue of The Amazing Spider-Man
did the Punisher first [laughter]
appear?
>> Over to you.
>> 143.
>> 129.
>> [laughter]
>> Pretty close.
>> Last question in round one. Who wrote
the original comics run of Brand New
Day?
>> Oh, damn.
>> We should all know this.
>> Embarrassing.
>> I'm sorry. We love you.
>> [laughter]
>> We love you.
>> The answer is
Dan Slott.
>> Dan Slott.
>> Sorry. Shout out.
>> Shout out.
>> Shout out to him.
>> Round two. This is MCU sort of wider MCU
multiverse knowledge.
>> Nice.
>> What high school did Peter, MJ, AND NED
ATTEND?
>> MIDTOWN.
>> FULL TITLE?
>> Midtown High.
>> Oh, sorry. Sorry.
>> I'll accept it.
>> Midtown School of SCIENCE AND
TECHNOLOGY.
>> MIDTOWN HIGH.
>> Science and Technology.
>> I'll accept it.
Question two. What did Peter say to
Doctor Strange after introducing himself
in Avengers: Infinity War?
>> Oh, I don't know.
>> I say, "Oh, we're mating our used up Oh,
no. No.
>> using
>> We're mating our We're mating our used
up
>> We're We're
>> used up
>> We're We're using our made up names.
>> That's what I was TRYING [laughter] TO
SAY.
>> YOU WERE JUMBLING, BRO. YOU WERE
STUMBLING, LIKE
>> [laughter]
>> I THINK I'M SO TIRED.
>> YOU WE'RE MATING OUR USED up names.
>> I just was helping.
>> Why do we keep We're mating our used up
>> We're using.
>> We're using our made up names. There you
go.
>> I think I'm going to have to give it to
Zendaya because you got to
>> She did fix it.
>> It's a half. Maybe we can split it.
>> In Spider-Man: No Way Home, what did
Peter 3, Andrew Garfield, think the
Avengers were?
Tom.
>> A band.
>> That's correct.
You want to contribute, John, at some
point?
>> He's coasting.
>> Yeah, I'm I'm sending good vibes.
>> [laughter]
>> I'm sending good vibes.
>> What pizza place did Peter Parker work
in the Sam Raimi Spider-Man 2?
>> Did that even go off?
>> Joe's Pizza.
>> That is correct, Jacob.
What villains did Peter Parker fight in
The Amazing Spider-Man 2?
>> Oh, man.
>> Tom.
>> Rhino, Electro, Green Goblin.
And that's it, right?
>> What was the name of Spider-Man's mecha
in the Japanese television series?
>> He's like He's like mecha suit. Mecha
mecha droid.
>> Yeah. Yeah.
>> [clears throat]
>> Mecha droid?
>> [laughter]
>> Leopardon.
>> I would not have got that.
>> It was a weird show, guys.
>> It's a deep cut.
>> Yeah, that's a deep cut. Round three,
this is production knowledge.
Who filmed Tom Holland's audition video?
>> Let's go.
>> [laughter]
>> YOU KNOW WHAT? I HIT IT FIRST. I'MMA LET
YOU have this though.
>> You're so awesome. Jonathan Edward
Bernthal.
>> Hey, let's go. Let's go. We'll give it
to John.
>> I got that last.
>> [laughter]
>> That's so pathetic.
>> What did Willem Dafoe wear on set to
prevent his appearance in Spider-Man No
Way Home from being leaked?
>> I honestly forgot.
>> I think that was Zendaya. That was you.
>> Who played Miles Morales' uncle in
Spider-Man Home?
>> Oh, man.
>> Donald Glover.
>> That's correct. Name both of Tom's stunt
doubles.
>> Jacob.
>> Uh Dave and Luke.
>> Yeah, that's technically correct. That's
technically correct.
>> And then there's a bunch of stunt
doubles. And then there's more.
>> And there's a Yeah, right. And the other
ones is from the other movies as well.
>> But that is That is technically correct.
>> We've had a lot, but yeah, that's
technically correct. Yeah.
>> Give it to Jacob.
>> All right. What two other Marvel
projects has Spider-Man Brand New Day
director Destin Daniel Cretton directed?
>> Wonder Man and Shang-Chi.
>> That's correct.
>> Yeah, yeah, it was It was close. It was
close.
>> Michael.
>> [laughter]
>> What show had Spider-Man's first
live-action appearance?
>> It's that TV show, isn't it?
>> Yeah,
he had his own TV show.
>> Yeah, I just didn't know what it was
called.
>> I
I thought it was called The Amazing
Spider-Man, right?
>> The electric company.
>> All right.
The way that you replied was like It was
like really close. Like you just
It was a TV show.
No, right. Yeah.
>> Okay, so this is finish the line. So
basically, I'm not going to tell you who
this said it, but if you can figure out
what the second half of the line is.
>> Okay.
>> Buzz in. You know I'm something of
>> A scientist
>> myself.
>> But he he I didn't hit it fast
>> yeah, I think Tom got it. That's my
secret, Cap.
>> What?
>> That's my secret, Cap.
>> That's your secret, Cap.
>> I didn't say that.
>> No, you didn't say that. No one here
said that.
>> Something Tony Stark would say?
>> secret, Cap.
>> But is it Spider-Man specific?
>> No.
>> I think I don't think so.
>> It's wider MCU. It's someone that is in
this movie
said this.
>> Oh, oh, oh, oh, it's it's it's
>> Yeah, you got it, below.
>> It's Mark Ruffalo, the Hulk. He says,
"Is time you get angry." And he goes,
"That's my secret, Cap. I'm always
angry." And then he goes
>> There you go. That's correct. That's
point to Tom.
Uh here's another one. One batch, two
batch.
>> Penny and Dime, let's go.
>> Damn, I would have never known.
[laughter]
>> That's another point for Dime.
>> It's crazy when that happens, isn't it?
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
>> Next line, the power of the sun.
>> In the palm of my hand.
>> That's correct, Otto Octavius. Awesome.
>> Oh, yeah. Right, when he's making like
that thing.
>> If you're nothing without this suit
then then you shouldn't have it.
>> Yeah, yeah.
>> Right, Tony Stark.
>> Yes.
>> Bang. Iron Man.
>> All right.
>> Well done.
>> I resent that. Slander is spoken.
>> Woah.
>> Can we hear it again?
>> [laughter]
>> Absolutely. I resent that. Slander is
spoken.
>> I don't know.
>> I'll give you a hint. Another line this
person typically says like, "I trust my
barber."
>> [laughter]
>> Give me PICTURES OF SPIDER-MAN.
>> OH, IT'S J. JONAH JAMESON.
>> WHAT IS
>> And the line is, "In print it's libel."
>> Spider-Man wasn't attacking the city. He
was trying to save it. That's slander.
>> It is not. I resent that.
Slander is spoken. In print it's libel.
>> You don't trust anybody. That's your
problem.
>> I trust my barber.
>> Um
>> I would never have gone to
>> I would never have figured that
out. I was going to finish it.
>> I'm trying to mess with you guys.
>> Yeah, I see you.
>> So
Round five is we're going to have a draw
Spider-Man competition. So you got to at
least win this one, bro. You you got to
hit this one.
I'm going to give you guys a minute.
>> Okay.
>> All right, in three, two, one. Go ahead.
>> is already good.
>> I made a bad shape. I made a bad shape.
>> Oh,
>> [laughter]
>> Oh, my god.
this up.
>> Oh, it's going sideways.
Sideways.
>> Yeah, I this up, all right, I
guess.
>> 10,
9, 8,
>> wears little boots, too, kind of.
>> 6,
>> Oh, yeah, there's little boots are
going.
>> 4, 3, [music] 2, 1. All right, pencils
down, everybody.
>> Okay.
>> [laughter]
>> I like the buildings.
>> Yeah, the building actually has no webs.
I like the spread out webs. Yeah, it
makes more sense.
>> A little abstract.
>> All right, you know. Jacob, let me see
what you got.
>> Okay.
>> All right, [laughter] you definitely
won.
>> Yeah, I think I think Sadie might have
killed it.
>> I'm going to say Sadie wins that.
>> You you didn't put
>> Yeah, the webs [laughter] are all there.
>> We just went with the belt.
>> Yeah.
>> Just the belt.
>> Yeah, the
>> You know, a simplified suit.
>> wear a belt?
>> That's really good.
>> That's a really great one.
>> It's an actual symbol of the video
game.
>> It's bad.
>> I [laughter] I started with this and
then I saw Zendaya.
>> Is that trying to get the eyes
different?
>> The grand formation.
>> Yeah, homie, yeah.
>> All right, so by vote, who do you think
won?
>> Is it Sadie?
>> Sadie.
>> Sadie, for sure.
>> Sadie?
>> There was so much detail.
>> And there's way more to it, yeah.
>> I
>> While Jacob wrecks the set, I'm going to
give Sadie the point by democratic vote.
So guys, this is the rapid fire round,
last round. How many Spider-Man films
there are there? Films starring
Spider-Man.
>> Eight. Nine.
>> Nine.
>> There's nine.
>> Bro, but
>> on. [clears throat]
>> Technically 14.
>> Damn. There was like any other
>> There's like other ones, yeah. Not just
not just the live action ones, yeah.
>> Who plays Spider-Man 2099 in Into the
Spider-Verse?
>> I don't know what his name is. The guy
with the
>> With the spikes.
>> He's like the
>> No, no, he's like the big like massive
one.
>> Like who plays Like who played or like
who does the voice?
>> Who does the voice?
>> I'll give you a hint. He is in
Star Wars and Dune and Inside Llewyn
Davis.
>> Oh, um
>> He's a He's a big guy.
>> Um
Wait, am I all of a sudden my brain is
not cannot function.
>> Yeah.
>> It's
>> Help me.
>> WE WE'RE NO,
WE'RE COMMUNICATING WITH EACH OTHER.
>> OSCAR ISAAC, OR GIVE IT TO ZENDAYA.
>> YEAH.
>> WHERE is Peter Parker from?
>> Queens.
>> Queens. Sadie, you were close, but
>> Sorry, Sadie.
>> It's all right. You can take it.
>> La Next question is what was Peter
Parker's first line in Captain America:
Civil War?
Tom.
>> Fine.
Hey, MAY.
>> FA FA
>> YEAH, HE
HEY, MAY. THEN I SAY FINE, THEN I SAY
something like there's a crazy car
parked outside. And then I see
>> Nice Peter Parker voice.
>> Thanks. Robert Downey Jr. Our next
question is what was the last thing
Peter said to Tony Stark in Avengers:
Infinity War?
Zendaya.
>> I don't want to go. I don't want to
And then
>> [laughter]
>> Are we We've been through this.
>> Nope.
>> It's not I don't want to go.
>> Tom, buzz in.
>> I say, "I'm sorry."
>> Oh. Perfect point for Tom.
>> And this one's a toughy.
When is the first time, technically,
that Spider-Man appeared alongside the
X-Men in live action?
>> Wait, wait, sorry.
>> Technically
>> When is the first time Spider-Man
appeared in live action alongside the
X-Men?
>> No idea.
>> Is it when he like went on to their set
one time and he like and it was like a
joke? Was it
>> Jacob, that is a 100% CORRECT.
>> [laughter]
>> YEAH, WELL, I REMEMBER watching this
video cuz I was up late at night and one
of them was like a random fact about
like 2002 movies.
And they were doing it at the same time,
right? They were like filming at the
same time or something like
>> Yeah, around the same time. Yeah, and
then it's a Blu-ray DVD extra.
>> Yes.
>> Wait.
>> [laughter]
>> Wow, I didn't think anyone was going to
get that.
>> That was good.
>> All right, so
>> I should win though.
>> I mean, for that
>> [laughter]
>> The final score is Sadie with one point.
John, you have two points. Jacob, you
came in with four points. Zendaya, you
have a total [music]
of seven points and Tom, you win this
pop quiz with a total of 10 points. You
are the winner of the GQ pop quiz.
>> Boo.
>> [laughter]
>> I've been playing this character for 10
years. It's the pride of my life. Seems
like you guys have got to do a little
bit more research before you grace the
sets yet again.
>> [laughter]
>> Thank you.
>> I don't know.
>> I don't know about that, yeah.
>> like we should we can run a few things
back.
>> Yeah, for sure. I'm going to laugh.
Yeah, for sure.
>> [laughter]